本字幕由Tao5133製作
卡梅隆特納 夥計
Cameron Turner, my man.
讓我猜猜 拿鐵、燕麥奶、不加糖
Let me guess. Latte, oat milk, no sugar.
沒錯 先生
Spot on, sir.
我要塊愛可巧克力棒 如果你有的話
I'll take an Echo bar if you've got any.
愛可我有得是 就這些嗎？
Echo's my middle name. Will that be all?
愛可牛奶巧克力
愛可我有得是 就這些嗎？
Echo's my middle name. Will that be all?
愛可牛奶巧克力
就這些 謝謝
That's good, thank you.
愛可牛奶巧克力
好的 已收款 請稍候
All right. Payment taken. Order coming up.
愛可牛奶巧克力
謝謝你 老弟
Thank you, bro.
不客氣 卡梅隆 很高興跟你聊 明天見
You're welcome, Cameron. Okay, good talk. We'll see you tomorrow.
到站乘客請下車
Step down from the train.
聽著 我瞭解我哥哥 好嗎？他很敏感
Look, I know my brother, all right? He's very sensitive.
愛可牛奶巧克力
喂？
Hello?
嘿 是
Hey. Yeah.
不 我們就要到站了
No. We're pulling into the station now.
本站是山頂公園
This station is Summit Park.
我們等會見 好嗎？好的
I'll see you in a bit, okay? All right.
再見
Bye.
都歸你
It's all yours.
列車到達山頂公園
The train is now arriving at Summit Park.
下一站是體院場大道
The next station is Stadium Avenue.
天啊
Oh, my God.
該死
Oh, fuck.
不
Oh, no.
見鬼
Oh, shit.
對不起 抱歉
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
卡梅隆
Cameron.
蘋果 原創 電影
出品
嗨 卡梅隆 我是斯科特醫生
Hi, Cameron. Dr. Scott here.
聽著 我不想再給你更多壓力
Look, I don't wanna add any more strain on you,
但是你最近的掃描顯示情況在加速惡化
but with your latest scan showing an accelerating deterioration,
所以至關重要的是我們要繼續…
it's vital that we keep moving forward with--
靜音
Mute.
小豬 你在外面嗎？
Pig. You out here?
好乖
Good boy, now.
你們給我留飯了嗎？
You guys save me some food?
是嗎？你今天沒把我的飯都吃掉？
Yeah? You didn't eat all my food today?
寇里的房間
小博士
神童還是未來的連環殺手？
Child prodigy or future serial killer?
非常期待家長會之夜
Can't wait for parent-teacher night.
今天的
家庭作業 鐘斯老師
嗷
天  鵝  挽  歌
歡迎來到艾拉之家 卡梅隆 很高興見到你本人
Welcome to Arra House, Cameron. Good to meet you in person.
請進
Come in.
這是我們的主要生活區
This is our main living area.
哇
Wow.
艾拉實驗室 同意書
艾拉實驗室 保密協議和最終同意
我知道其中一些理念會讓人不舒服
I know that some of these concepts are uncomfortable.
艾拉實驗室 保密協議和最終同意
我知道其中一些理念會讓人不舒服
I know that some of these concepts are uncomfortable.
只要記住如果你在評估過程中的任何時刻
Just remember that if you decide not to proceed
決定不再繼續下去 他就永遠不會離開這裡
at any point in the evaluation process, he never leaves this facility.
那麼…他絕對不會有我的病？
And there's-- there's no way he gets this thing?
正如這裡所列出的 我們調整了他的相關DNA鏈
As outlined, we modified the relevant strands of his DNA
以防止再發生這種情況
to prevent that happening again.
如果我決定不進行 他會怎麼樣？他就…
And what happens to him if I decide not to do this? He just--
他會在當天晚上毫不知情地睡去 什麼都不會知道
He goes to sleep that night unaware. Doesn't know a thing.
我們暫時稱他為傑克 如果你同意這個名字
We'll be calling him Jack for now, if that name's okay with you.
這是控制室
This is the control room.
這是道爾頓
And this is Dalton.
-歡迎你 卡梅隆 -你好
-Welcome, Cameron. -Hello.
他是一名心理學家 也是我們的首席技術員
He's a psychologist and the head technician.
這就是我們團隊
And that completes our team.
只有你們三個人？
It's just three of you?
三個人類 我們的人工智慧系統 承擔大約50個人的工作
Three humans. Our AI systems do the work of about 50 people.
在我們讓你進入之前
Before we let you in,
我們需要你關掉 隱形眼鏡和手錶中的攝像頭
we'll need you to disable the cameras in your contacts and your watch.
好吧
Oh, okay.
關閉攝像頭
Disable cameras.
謝謝
Thank you.
那我們進去吧？
So, shall we go in?
通過分子再生創造
Molecularly regenerated.
與你的DNA完全相同
Mapped to your DNA.
精確到分子的卡梅隆特納
Cameron Turner to the molecule.
他在做夢嗎？
Is he dreaming?
還沒有
Not yet.
請吧 他不會醒來
Go ahead. He can't wake.
我很抱歉 醫生
I'm sorry, Doctor.
我不能這麼做
I can't do this.
我理解這對你是一個多麼重大的決定
I know what a momentous decision this is for you.
我知道你正在經歷些什麼
I know what you're going through.
短信息
斯科特醫生
線上
新聞
32分鐘前更新 到達時間
20分鐘後 我理解這對你是
一個多麼重大的決定
我知道你正在經歷些什麼
只是…
But just…
短信息
斯科特醫生
線上
新聞
32分鐘前更新 到達時間
20分鐘後 我理解這對你是
一個多麼重大的決定
我知道你正在經歷些什麼
短信息
斯科特醫生
線上
新聞
32分鐘前更新 到達時間
20分鐘後 我理解這對你是
一個多麼重大的決定
我知道你正在經歷些什麼
你一旦告訴你妻子你快死了
the second you tell your wife that you're dying,
短信息
斯科特醫生
線上
新聞
32分鐘前更新 到達時間
20分鐘後 我理解這對你是
一個多麼重大的決定
我知道你正在經歷些什麼
你一旦告訴你妻子你快死了
the second you tell your wife that you're dying,
你做此事的機會就消失了
your opportunity to do this is gone.
你可以告訴她
You can tell her,
或者你可以跟我們合作 讓你家人的生活繼續下去
or you can do this with us and let life go on for your family.
但鑒於你持續惡化的情況 我們拖延不起 卡梅隆
But given your worsening condition, we can't afford to delay, Cameron.
請給我回電
Please call me.
斑頭海番鴨
A surf scoter.
好極了 那這個呢？
Excellent. And this one?
寇里？
Cory?
冠頂秋沙鴨
Hooded mergant.
牛角包
不
No.
能不能給我你的鉛筆？
Can I have your pencils?
-你想要我的鉛筆了？ -嗯哼
You eyeing my pencils now?
我用了22年的那套鉛筆 你想要了？
The same set I've had for 22 years. You're eyeing my pencils?
反正你現在也沒在使
You ain't using 'em.
“沒在使”？ 我們什麼時候開始這麼說話了？
"Ain't"? When did we start saying "ain't"?
自從安德列死了 你就不用了
You don't use 'em since Andre died.
卡梅 你最近是怎麼回事？
Cam, what's with you lately?
聽著 我知道你是藝術家 這對你來說很痛苦 我明白
Look, I know you're an artist and this is painful for you. I get it.
可這是一種注重健康的有機茶
But this is a health-focused organic tea.
我們不是在設計什麼該死的死藤水
It's not some fucking ayahuasca brew we're designing.
當你按照客戶的要求去做 你會圓滿完成任務 你明白嗎？
When you follow along with what the client wants, you kill it, you know?
所以按照要求做就好 行嗎？
So just play ball. Okay?
-好吧 -愛你 再見
-All right. -Love ya. Bye.
有機
散葉茶
你想吃嗎？
You want one of these?
有機
散葉茶
新短信
斯科特醫生
-安德列舅舅 -寇里 說“安德列舅舅”？
-Uncle Andre. -Cory, can you say "Uncle Andre"?
順便一提 那就是克隆
That is cloning, by the way.
-不 -是的
-No! -Yeah.
不 嚴格來說 那不是 文章說那不是
No, technically speaking, it's not. The article said it's not.
是…再生
It's-- It's regeneration.
不管你叫它什麼 安德列 那還是怪怪的
It doesn't matter what you call it, Andre. It's still weird.
我不管他們說那項技術有多麼先進
I don't care how good they say the tech's gonna be.
你會立刻知道那不是一個真人
You'd know it wasn't a real person in seconds.
聽著 我只是說 從理論上來說
Look, I'm just saying, hypothetically speaking,
如果那真的可能呢？ 如果他們真的研究出來了呢？
what if it was actually possible? What if they did actually work it out?
不可能 安德列 因為你無法複製一個人 你做不到
They won't, Andre. 'Cause you can't copy a human being. You can't.
-卡梅隆 -不 我不…參與這個對話
-Cameron? -No. I-- No, I'm staying way out of this.
少來
Oh, come on.
再沒有比一大早討論死亡更喪的了
Nothing like a good death chat first thing in the morning.
好吧
Okay.
-好笑是嗎？ -對嗎？太可笑了
-Is that funny? -Right? It's ridiculous. Come on.
聽著 如果媽媽可以現在 跟我們在這裡坐在一起
Look, if Mom could be sitting here right now with us,
我們看不出來 她完全一模一樣 那我就同意
and, like, you know, we couldn't tell, she was indistinguishable, then yeah.
去他的倫理道德吧 我可以接受
You know, screw the ethics. I would take that.
儘管這麼說
I mean, that being said,
如果他們碰巧刪除了她對遊艇搖滾的喜愛
if they happen to delete her fondness for yacht rock,
-我不會傷心欲絕 -對
-I would not be devastated. -Yes.
太瘋狂了 學學她的嘴唇 波比 學學她的嘴唇
Going crazy. Gimme the lips, Poppy. Gimme the lips.
就是這樣
There it is.
是的
Yes.
我們能見面嗎？
我理解你的感受 但這裡不存在謊言
I know how you're feeling, but there is no lie.
當關於這個過程的記憶被抹去
When the memory of this process gets wiped,
他會在那一天作為卡梅隆特納在家裡醒來
he wakes up that day at home as Cameron Turner.
沒有人知道 連他自己都不知道
And no one knows. Not even him.
這是唯一奏效的辦法 乾淨徹底的交換
It's the only way this works. A clean swap.
還有多少其他的人？我想知道
How many others are out there? I wanna know.
你是我們的第三個
You'll be our third.
在幾年之內 這將會像心臟移植手術一樣平常
This will be as common as a heart transplant within a few years.
回來和他共處一周 然後你再做決定
Come back and spend a week with him before making your decision.
這不僅僅是我的決定 我妻子必須知道
This is not just my decision. My wife needs to know.
要麼你決定這是你妻子所希望的 那就必須保密
Either you decide that your wife would want this, which requires secrecy,
要麼你決定她不希望這樣 那就告訴她你快死了
or you decide that she wouldn't, and tell her you're dying.
無論如何 是你在為她做決定
Either way, you're deciding for her.
聽著 你將見到的女人 根本不知道她是克隆人
Listen, the woman you're about to meet has no idea she's a duplicate.
凱特喬房地產
聽著 你將見到的女人 根本不知道她是克隆人
Listen, the woman you're about to meet has no idea she's a duplicate.
凱特喬房地產
她的女兒、母親或朋友都不知道
Neither does her daughter, her mother, or her friends.
那麼有什麼謊言可言呢？
So, where is the lie?
你好 你是特納先生 對嗎？
Oh, hey, there. Mr. Turner, right?
是 卡梅隆
Yeah, uh, Cameron.
想在這個區找三間臥室的房子？
Browsing for a three-bed in the neighborhood?
是的
Oh, yeah.
這是我的老闆 薩曼莎
This is, uh, my boss, Samantha.
我是她女兒
I'm her daughter.
女兒
Daughter.
她是個嚴厲的老闆
She runs a tight ship.
總之 請坐吧
Anyway, have a seat.
正好我今天拿到一些好房子
I had some good ones come in today, actually.
你給我的資訊裡說你有一個兒子 對嗎？
You said in your message you had a son, right?
是的 寇里
Yeah. Cory.
他也是你家的老闆？
He runs the show as well?
對 年齡越小脾氣越大
Yeah. The smaller, the bossier.
-嘿-嘿
-Hey. -Hey.
-怎麼樣？ -很好
-Yeah? -Yeah.
寇里在傑西家吃晚飯？
Cory at Jessie's for dinner?
對 他8點回來
Yeah. He's back at 8:00.
-你在休息嗎？ -是
-You taking a break? -Yeah.
我想我們會讓赫伯特醫生做超聲波檢查
So I think we're gonna get Dr. Herbert for the ultrasound.
我在等他們確認 不過很有希望
I'm just waiting for them to confirm, but it's looking good.
是
Yeah.
太好了 我們喜歡赫伯特
That's good. We like Herbert.
你準備好面對性感的保齡球肚皮了嗎？
Are you bracing yourself for sexy bowling ball bod?
我還是不敢相信
I still can't believe it.
我們又要愛上一個小傢伙了
We're gonna fall in love with a new little person again.
七個月
Seven months.
怎麼了 卡梅？
What's up, Cam?
我沒事 只是…
I'm good. It's just, um…
只是…
It's just, um…
那麼我們…
So, we, um…
卡梅隆？
Cameron?
只是 一個新的小生命…
It's just, a new little person. And…
我想我還在適應當中
I think that's just sinking in still, you know.
熊熊
Oh, bear.
卡梅
Cam.
我知道我用了很長時間
I know it took me a minute,
我也知道我們的關係最近不太和諧
and I know we haven't been us for a while,
但這個寶寶會對我們有好處
but this baby is going to be good for us.
是啊
Yeah.
我們會沒事的 好嗎？
We're gonna be okay. All right?
寇里
Cory.
卡梅隆
Cameron?
我改變主意了
I've changed my mind.
我可以坐下嗎？
Mind if I sit?
嗨 我是…卡梅隆
Hi. I'm Cameron.
凱特
Kate.
你見到她了？
So, you met her?
昨天
Yesterday.
她怎麼樣？
How's she doing?
挺好的 大概吧
Good. I guess.
她想賣房子給你？
She try to sell you a house?
康鬥
Condo.
那是我們的工作
It's what we do.
一周？
A week?
客戶今天突然這樣要求 根本沒有提前通知？
And the clients just spring this on you today, zero notice?
卡梅 發生什麼事了？
What's going on, Cam?
沒事
Nothing.
他們的設計師突然病倒 他們需要一個人在現場
The designer they had got sick last minute and they needed someone here in person.
聽著 我很抱歉 波 真的
Look, I'm sorry, P. I am.
我真希望我現在不必離開你 相信我
I wish I didn't have to be away right now. Believe me.
好吧 我得過去了
All right. Well, I'd better get back here.
-我們回頭再聊 好嗎？ -好的
-I'll speak to you later, yeah? -All right.
好吧 卡梅隆
Okay, Cameron.
整個過程中你都會無知覺 大約需要六個小時
You'll be out for the entire process. It'll take about six hours.
好吧 他什麼都會有？
Okay. He'll have everything?
全部的記憶
Every single memory
一直到你在那把椅子中失去知覺的那一刻
right up to the moment you lose consciousness in that chair.
幾秒鐘之後你就會失去知覺
In a few moments, you're gonna go under.
好的 我想我…
Okay. I think I--
我…
I thi--
你享受這一刻 你享受這一天
Like, you having a moment. You having a day.
謝謝
Thank you.
那麼他全都有了？
So, he has everything?
甚至包括你深藏在潛意識中的記憶
Even the memories you've stored deep in your subconscious.
所有那些記憶 它們不僅是我的
All those memories, they're not just mine.
它們也是我…妻子的、我兒子的
They're my wife's, my son's.
而不是什麼實驗的一部分
Not part of some experiment.
我真希望我能跟她談談
I just wish I could talk to her.
當他們把我的2.0版本送回去
When they sent "me 2.0" back,
看到我媽媽注視著她的眼睛 不知道那不是我
seeing my mom look into her eyes not knowing it wasn't me,
看到她跟我女兒說話
seeing her talking to my daughter…
我是說…
I mean…
然後當他們抹去她的記憶
And then when they wiped her…
知道她不再是這個謊言的參與者 我的內疚感很快就消失了
knowing she was no longer in on the lie, my guilt faded pretty quick.
我們有同一個腫瘤醫生 你知道嗎？
We share an oncologist, you know?
克羅西馬醫生？
Dr. Kerosima?
對
Yep.
我之前的病人也是她的病人
The patient before me was a patient of hers too.
她看起來很快樂 你女兒 她們都很快樂
She seemed happy, your daughter. They both did.
是嗎？
Yeah?
她在外面多久了？
How long has she been out there?
大約…
Roughly…
42天零6小時
forty-two days, six hours.
大約？
Roughly?
差不多吧
Ballpark.
記憶對照檢查讓我們能夠確認
Memory cross-checks allow us to make sure
他的意識內和潛意識內的記憶
that his conscious and subconscious memories
完全符合你的記憶
are perfectly in sync with yours.
開始可能感覺有些奇怪
It will feel strange at first.
你只要努力停留在每個記憶中
Just try to stay in each memory.
你什麼時候開始都行 卡梅隆
In your own time, Cameron.
嗨
Hi.
卡梅隆 我喜歡你的畫
Cameron, I like your picture.
呼吸
Breathe.
這感覺真實 因為對你的大腦而言 它就是真的
It feels real because as far as your brain is concerned, it is real.
只是倒回去了好多年
Just, skipped way back.
這很正常
That's normal.
隨著系統的進步 它會測試任何時間點
As it progresses, the system will test any point in time
一直回到出生的時候
all the way back to birth.
你需要努力停留在記憶中 這非常重要
It's vital that you do your best to stay in the memories
不要打斷過程 好嗎？
and not break the flow, okay?
好的
Okay.
你準備好就開始
When you're good.
嗨 還記得我嗎？ 幾周前我們見過
Hi, remember me from a few weeks back?
是的 你吃了我的巧克力棒
Yeah. You ate my chocolate bar.
是這樣 我也買了一個愛可巧克力棒
See, I also purchased an Echo bar.
我…希望你現在已經搞明白了
And I'm hoping you worked that out by now. Yeah.
我真希望看到你意識到時臉上的表情
Yeah. I'd have loved to see your face when you realized.
不是我的榮耀時刻
Not a strong moment for me.
我剛看見你坐在那裡
I just saw you, um, just sitting here,
我就…畫了這個
and I-- I made this thing.
在我包裡
It's in my bag.
給你
Here you go.
哇 你畫得真好
Wow! Wow, you're good.
謝謝 我現在意識到
Oh, thank you. I realize now
這讓我更像一個神經病了
that even makes me look more like a psycho.
-噢 是嗎？ -不過我不是…我保證
-Oh, yeah? -But I'm not! I'm not. I promise.
有才華的神經病 比沒才華的神經病強 所以…
A talented psycho is better than a talentless one, so…
是啊 謝謝你這麼說
Yeah. I appreciate that.
對了 我…叫卡梅隆
I'm Cameron, by the way.
卡梅隆 我叫波比
Cameron. Poppy.
波比
Poppy.
幸會
Pleasure.
我要到站了
My stop's coming up.
好的 好吧 那就再見吧
Oh, okay. Um, all right. Well, I'll let you go.
很抱歉我吃了你的巧克力棒
Sorry again for eating your candy bar.
我希望回頭再碰見你
I hope to see you around.
-下一站是山頂公園 -好吧 萬事如意
-The next station is Summit Park. -All right, best wishes.
萬事如意
Best wishes.
嘿 卡梅隆
Hey, Cameron?
給你
Here.
不 那是給你的 留著吧
Oh, no, that's for you. Keep it.
你下次再給我
Give it to me again.
好吧
Okay.
波比
Poppy.
-怎麼樣？害怕了嗎？ -有一點害怕
-Yeah? Are you scared yet? -I'm a little bit scared.
畫裡的內容很豐富的
Like, there's a lot going on there.
你是說那天我做的那個糟糕的東西嗎？
You mean that awful thing I made the other day?
好
Yes!
讓我出來
Let me out.
你再等等 我還沒準備好迎接你
You hold on a little bit. I'm not ready for you.
我們等你很久了
We've been waiting so long for you.
她讓我想起寇里 你好乖
She reminds me so much of Cory. You're so sweet.
然後有第三個
And then there was a third one.
我不想看你 那讓我發笑
I don't wanna look at you. It makes me laugh.
媽媽
Mommy.
-我不回去 -沒事的
-I'm not going back in. -It's okay.
我看見她在樓上她的房間裡
I saw her upstairs in her room,
她在哭泣 她看起來很傷心
and she was crying, and she looked really sad.
是因為安德列嗎？
Is it because of Andre?
卡梅隆特納 這是我的雙胞胎兄弟 安德列
Cameron Turner, my twin brother, Andre.
嗨 安德列
Hey, Andre.
-我本應該阻止他 -不…
-I should have stopped him. -No, no, no, no.
我本該阻止他
I should have stopped him.
都怪我 卡梅 都怪我
It's my fault, Cam. It's my fault.
-我… -卡梅隆 你沒事吧？
-I-- -You good, Cameron?
-對不起 給我一分鐘 -好吧
-I'm sorry. I need a second. -All right.
好吧 我們繼續
All right. Let's go.
你現在安排休假了？
You're booking days off now?
對 我安排了休假 這樣等我回來 我們就可以共度時光
Yeah, I booked time off so we can hang out when I get back.
這過去的六個月 我一直試圖把你從辦公桌前拉開
I've been trying to peel you away from your desk for the last six months.
突然你就要毅然決然地放下一切
Suddenly you're gung-ho to drop everything.
我知道 你說得對 是…
I know. You're right. It's--
熊熊？
Bear?
-你沒事吧？ -沒事
-You good? -Yeah. Yes.
是嗎？
Yeah?
你確定你對這件事開心嗎？
Are you sure you're happy about this?
過去這兩周你…
Yeah. The last couple of weeks you just…
我不知道 只是…
I don't know. Just--
嘿 波 我沒事 都是因為工作 我在工作
Hey, P. I'm fine. It's just work. I'm working.
我…只是不喜歡離開你而已
I… I just hate being away from you. That's all.
我很想念我們
And I just miss us.
等我回到家 我們好好談談 好嗎？
When I get home, we're gonna hang out and talk for real, okay?
好的 卡梅隆
Okay, Cameron.
我的天
Oh, my God.
好吧 這件東西一定是你的錯
Okay, you're definitely taking the blame for this specimen.
不 我相信是寇里自己挑的
No. I believe Cory picked that out himself.
-什麼？在三個月大的時候？ -是的 因為我跟他在一起
-What? At three months? -Yeah. Because I was with him.
我們在商店裡轉悠
We were in the store walking around,
我推著坐在嬰兒車裡的他 他說：“嘿 你 老大
and I'm pushing him in the stroller. And he's like, "Hey. Yo, big man.
你看見那件芥末黃的連身衣了嗎？
You see that yellow mustard onesie right there?
我的人生需要它”
I need that in my life."
是啊 他那麼有魅力 我說“嘿 你覺得怎麼樣？”
Yeah, he's so charming. I was like, "Hey, what do you say to that?"
對 他是很有魅力 這個我同意
Yeah, he is very charming. I'll give you that.
可是這簡直是犯罪
But this is criminal.
你和我一起照顧她
Together, me and you will take care of her
直到她可以自己照顧自己 好嗎？
till she can take care of herself again. All right?
我們倆都得為了她堅強一些 好嗎？ 她現在只是生病了
Me and you gotta be strong for her, okay? She's just sick right now.
走開
Go away.
醒來吧 小子 快點
Wake up, man. Come on.
至少再睡六個小時
At least six more hours.
再睡六個小時？
Six more hours?
外面天還黑著呢 看
It's still dark outside. Look!
因為天還早 可是你得醒來了 孩子 我們得走了
'Cause it's early. But you gotta wake up, man. We gotta go.
放開這只手 對了 轟
Let this hand go. There, boom.
-現在轉動手腕 隨球動作 -進了
-And now flick it. Follow through. -Boom.
一、二、三
我曾經整天在我房間裡玩這個
I used to do this all day in my room.
-真好聞 -是嗎？
-That smells so good. -You think?
-羽衣甘藍…薄荷… -是的 對了
-Kale. Kale. Kale. Mint. And mint. -Yes. All right.
把它蘸…一點醬油
Dip 'em in a little-- a little soy sauce.
好了 我在這裡待命
Okay. I'm standing by up here.
需要多長時間？
How long will it take?
他應該馬上醒來
He should wake instantly.
好的 我們這裡準備好了
Okay. We're ready to go up here.
好吧
All right.
好
Okay.
閉著你的眼睛
Keep your eyes closed.
我給你從三開始倒數
I'm gonna count you down from three.
三…
And on three…
二…
And two…
一
And one.
你沒事
You're okay.
呼吸
Breathe.
-就是這樣？ -就是這樣
-That's it? -That's it.
一切順利？
Everything go okay?
一切非常順利
Everything went great.
我什麼時候能見他？
When will I see him?
明天早上
In the morning.
在那之前 你應該好好睡一覺
Until then, you should get some sleep.
你在這裡的這段時間
For the time that you are in this facility,
這個斑點是你全身
that freckle is the only place on your entire body
唯一跟他不同的地方
that isn't identical to his.
如果你弄混了
If you get confused,
你找到那個斑點 就知道自己是誰了 好嗎？
you find that freckle and you'll know who you are. Okay?
我們理解這種感覺多麼奇怪
We know how strange this is.
你這樣做非常合算
You got the good deal here.
你會明白的
You'll see.
砰 再來
Boom! Again.
-來點下巴音樂 -你要輸了
-Little chin music. -You're going down.
你根本不懂 孩子
You don't know nothing about this, boy.
你太年輕
You too young.
沒門 傻小子
Chump.
好耶
Yeah!
砰
Boom!
-太棒了 -又一個偷偷摸摸的左勾拳
-Yeah, baby! -That's just another cheap left.
結束通話
End call.
爸爸？
Dad?
-嘿 卡梅隆 -說話呀 卡梅隆
-Hey, Cameron? -Talk to me, Cameron.
-不 -給波比發信息
-No. -Send Poppy a message.
他們說我會死於任何一次癲癇發作
They're saying any of these seizures could kill me.
在回去看他們之前 我有可能這周就死在這裡
And I could die out here this week before getting home to see them.
我無法停止想像她得到消息 不得不告訴寇里
I can't stop picturing her getting the news, having to tell Cory.
波比和我經歷了一些事情
Poppy and I had been going through some stuff.
那天晚上我讓她笑了
The other night I made her laugh.
我不記得上次讓她笑是什麼時候 你懂嗎？
I can't remember the last time I did that, you know?
讓她發笑
Just made her laugh.
那是因為你不風趣
That's because you're not funny.
對 那也是原因
Yeah, that too.
那種東西會致死
Those things will kill you, you know.
你其實挺風趣的 去他的
Oh, you are funny. Fuck that.
卡梅隆
Cameron?
我們一切就緒了
We're ready for you.
回頭見
See you later.
玩得開心
Have fun.
波比是世界上最能睡的人
Poppy's the world's best sleeper.
她累了的時候 幾秒鐘之內就能睡著
When she's tired, she'll just drift off in seconds,
就像燈一下子滅了
like, out like a light.
波比會說法語？
Poppy speaks French?
她依舊偶爾說些法語詞
Yeah, she'll still say the occasional French word.
比如 她會說 “晚安”
Like, she'll say…
或者…
Or…
“怎麼樣 那不可能”
如果什麼事情很棒 非常完美
Or if something is great, like, just perfect,
她可能會小聲說…
she might whisper…
完美
“真完美”
你想去打個招呼嗎？
You wanna go say hi?
你好嗎？
You okay?
昨晚之後？
After last night?
挺好的
Good.
我不知道如何…
I don't know how to…
說什麼
What to say here.
我知道你不認為我…
I know you don't think I'm…
是你…
You.
我坐在那個房間看著拉法
I'm sitting up in that room, looking at Rafa.
我的心臟劇烈跳動 我很緊張
My heart is beating out of my chest, and, um, I'm nervous.
我真的很緊張
I'm really nervous.
然後爸爸突然出現在我腦海裡
Then Dad pops in my head.
他們離婚後 第一次去看他
That first trip out to see him after they split.
登上那駕飛機
Getting on that airplane.
緊張得要命 你知道嗎？
Just the nerves, you know?
我閉上眼
And I close my eyes.
然後睜開
And then I open 'em.
我不在那個房間裡了
I'm not up there in that room anymore.
我在這裡
I'm here.
我就在這裡
I am here.
我很抱歉 夥計 我很抱歉…
I'm sorry, man. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
他知道你很緊張 傑克
He knows you're nervous, Jack.
只要回答問題就好
Just answer the questions.
-關閉音訊 -卡梅隆
-Audio muted. -Cameron…
你就是你
you're you.
不存在錯誤的答案
There are no wrong answers.
音訊恢復
Audio unmuted.
好的 傑克 波比從事兒童工作
Okay, Jack. Poppy works with children.
對 她教有學習困難的兒童
Yeah, she teaches kids with learning difficulties
通過音樂療法
through music therapy.
她對奧爾夫舒維克教學法有獨特的見解
She's got her own take on the Orff Schulwerk method.
她和孩子們創作音樂 把他們放到歌曲中
So, um, she makes songs with the kids, and she puts them in the songs.
他們很喜歡
And… they love it.
她就是才華橫溢
She's just insanely talented.
她在乎 你知道嗎？她真的很在乎
She cares. You know? Like, she really cares.
你一直都想要孩子嗎？
Did you always want children?
我喜歡這個 卡梅隆特納
I like this, Cameron Turner.
我想我是在認識波比後 意識到自己想要孩子
I think after I met Poppy, I realized I wanted kids.
這些我都喜歡
I like all of this.
是
Yeah.
我憤世嫉俗了很長時間
I was cynical for a long time.
哇 天啊
Wow. Oh, my gosh.
我們對書的品味相似得令人害怕
We have scarily similar taste in books.
找到真愛或心靈伴侶的想法
This idea of finding true love or a soul mate.
J迪拉 甜甜圈
找到真愛或心靈伴侶的想法
This idea of finding true love or a soul mate.
J迪拉 甜甜圈
然後像波比這樣的人突然出現 你意識到你只是在生存
Then someone like Poppy comes along and you realize you're just surviving.
你演奏音樂嗎？
Do you play?
我亂彈一氣
I butcher.
不過我可不要在你面前演奏
But I'm not playing in front of you.
我本來會就那樣混下去
I could have just gone on like that forever.
你最好停下 想想你在做什麼
You better stop And think about what you doing
我喜歡 好
Oh, I love it. Yes.
我想我實在太幸運了
I just lucked out, I guess.
很好
Good.
說說你父母的關係
Talk about your parents' relationship.
其實沒什麼可說的
Well, there's not really much to talk about.
我五歲的時候他們離婚了 我爸爸因為工作原因搬家了
They divorced when I was five, and my dad moved away for work.
他是個醫生 兒科醫生…
He was a doctor. A pediatrician.
他看起來像我、聲音像我 可我不知道…
He looks like me. He sounds like me, but I don't know…
七個月之後 那個孩子就會來到世上 沒有爸爸
In seven months, that child is gonna come into the world without a dad.
七個月
Seven months.
嘿 至少你不為自己難過
Hey. At least you're not feeling sorry for yourself.
好吧 這很公平
Oh, okay. That's fair.
你會沒事的 夥計
You're gonna be good, man.
這很公平
That's fair.
那你呢？你怎麼樣？
And what about you? How you doing?
我？
Me?
從來沒這麼好過
Never better.
還有別的好問題嗎？
Any other great questions?
沒有 好吧
No. Okay.
對
Yep.
在這裡我真是開心極了
Having the time of my life out here.
美麗的大自然 美味的食物
Nature's awesome. Great food.
卡梅隆
Cameron?
說一個隱晦的
Make it obscure.
安德列 禮物
Andre. Gift.
我會喜歡嗎？
Am I actually gonna like this?
-大概不會 也許… -天啊 什麼？
-Probably not. It's probably-- -Oh, God. What?
-把腳抬高 -把腳抬到哪？
-Lift your feet up high. -Lift my feet up where?
-走… -不行 不…
-And step. Step. Step. -Whoa! Oops. Oh, no! No! Oh.
對了…
There we go. There you go.
很安全…
We're safe. We're safe.
是什麼啊？
What is it?
你送我一台鋼琴
You got me a piano!
安德列
Andre!
天啊
Oh, my God.
-太謝謝你了 -他跟波比太像了
-Thank you so much. -And he was so like Poppy.
超級聰明 人又溫柔
Like, just wildly smart and gentle.
他出了什麼事？
What happened to him?
安德列在一條山路上行駛時 從摩托車上摔下
Andre… was thrown from his bike off of a mountain road.
他的身體落在一棵很高的松樹上
His body landed in the branches of a pine tree, high up.
每隔幾周我都會夢見他在樹梢上
Every couple of weeks, I dream about him up there in the treetops.
獨自一人躺在那裡
Alone. Just laying there.
你跟你妻子談過那個夢嗎？
Have you talked to your wife about that dream?
沒有
No.
為什麼沒有？
Why not?
那一年她有一大半時間都沒出門
She didn't leave the house for the better part of a year.
大部分時間睡在客房
Slept in the guest room most of that time, so…
我只想幫你
I'm just trying to help you.
我知道…
I know, I know.
-我需要獨自待著 謝謝 -拜託…
-I need to be alone. Thank you. -Please--
那不是我們想要提起的話題
It's not really subject matter we enjoy getting into.
波比睡在別處讓你有何感受？
How did Poppy sleeping apart make you feel?
孤獨
Alone.
主要是我擔心她
Mostly, I worried about her.
我想念她
I missed her.
你有沒有為此怨恨她？
Did you resent her for it?
她失去了雙胞胎兄弟
She lost her twin.
她一直對他買那輛摩托車感到不安
She never felt good about him getting that motorcycle.
責怪自己沒有更強烈地反對
Blamed herself for not protesting more.
可是他無論如何是要買那輛摩托車的
But he was gonna get the bike anyway.
你說過波比在治療師的幫助下取得了很大進展
You've mentioned how well Poppy has progressed with her therapist
就在過去的這幾個月
over the last few months.
但你從來沒有找過治療師？
But you never went to see anybody?
沒有
No.
在你父母離婚後 你跟任何人談過嗎？
Did you talk to someone after your parents were divorced?
沒有 我當時才五歲
No, I was five.
那麼你從來沒有看過心理治療師？
So you've never been to a therapist?
沒有
No.
你不能告訴波比這個你反復做的夢？
And you can't talk to Poppy about this dream that you keep having?
已經兩年了 為什麼你沒有去看過治療師？
It's been two years. Why haven't you gone to see somebody?
我不知道
I don't know.
卡梅隆
Cameron?
抱歉 我…
I'm sorry, I--
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
沒關係
It's okay.
我們休息一下
Let's take a break.
給你留的
Saving them for you.
好了
All right.
傑克 你準備好了嗎？
Jack, are you ready?
好了
Yeah.
-卡梅隆呢？ -好了
-Cameron? -Yeah.
好吧
All right.
請給波比打電話
Call Poppy, please.
這也太湊巧了吧 我剛跟診所通了話
This is weird timing. I just spoke to the clinic.
已經確認了赫伯特醫生 在25號給我做超聲波檢查
Doctor Herbert is confirmed for the ultrasound on the 25th.
卡梅？
Cam?
這太真實了
That's real.
是啊 很真實 身體裡有個小生命
Yeah. So real. Living human in body.
感覺和我記憶中寇里那次完全不同 對嗎？
Just feels so different to how I remember it with Cory, right?
是啊
Yeah.
你記得我們是怎麼知道的嗎？
Remember how we found out?
天啊 是啊 那場大雪
Oh, my God, yeah. That insane snow.
第二天是傑西和柔伊的婚禮
Jessie and Zoe's wedding the next day.
柔伊馬上就知道了
Zoe knew right away.
“天啊 你懷孕了 波比”
"Oh, my God. You're pregnant, Poppy."
我記得那種感覺
Oh, I remember that feeling.
你還沒走出醫生辦公室
You were barely out of the doctor's office,
就已經在製作播放清單 把音箱放在這裡
you were already making a playlist, holding the speaker there.
是啊 對 子宮音樂
Yeah. Yes. Womb tunes.
子宮音樂 那是好久以前了
Womb tunes. Oh, it's been a minute.
嘿 我們也應該儘快告訴寇里
Hey, we should tell Cory soon, too.
對 我也這麼想…
Yeah, I was thinking the same--
拉法 給波比發條信息
Rafa, send Poppy a message.
-你做什麼？ -我不喜歡這樣
-What did you do? -I don't like this.
你以為我喜歡嗎？ 在聚光燈下跟我的妻子說話？
And you think I like this? Talking to my wife under a spotlight?
她不是你的妻子
She's not your wife!
好吧…我明白了
Oh, okay. Okay, I see.
你受不了看到這實際上是奏效的 這才是真正的問題
You can't bear to see this actually work. That's the real problem.
-去死吧 -你去死
-Fuck you, man! -Fuck you!
我怎麼了？在這裡地方醒來
And what about me? Waking up in this place,
等著你拔掉電源 被告知我不是我
waiting for you to pull the plug, being told I'm not me.
因為你不是我
Because you're not me.
你不是我
You are not me!
算了 讓這見鬼去吧
You know what? Fuck all this.
-不 狗屁 你哪也別去 -這是狗屁 見鬼去吧
-No, bullshit. You stay right here. -This is bullshit! Fuck that!
-你別走 少來 這是真的 -打開門
-Stay here. Bullshit. This is real. -Open the fucking door!
你知道的…
And you know it. You know it.
波比說如果她看不出來 如果她的媽媽沒有任何區別…
Poppy said if she couldn't tell, if her mom was indistinguishable…
這就是了 沒有任何區別
Well, here it is. Indistinguishable.
你不想做這件事 因為你太自私
You won't go through with it because you're too selfish!
別碰我
Get the fuck off me.
我不想看見你了
I'm done with you. Huh?
想做嗎？做吧 你去死 做吧…
Do something? Do it. Fuck you, do it. Do it!
對 你不會離開這裡的
Yeah. You won't leave this place.
我會回家去 我會告訴他們所有事 所有事
I'm going home, and I'm telling them everything. Everything!
好呀 我打賭你會的 王八蛋
Yeah, I bet you will. Bitch ass.
你一直只關心自己…
It's always about you. It's always about you.
她一直想跟你談 我都不知道多久了
She's been trying to talk for I don't know how long,
你一直在躲避她
and you keep shutting her out,
因為在你內心深處 你覺得她拋棄了我們
because deep down inside, you feel like she abandoned us.
-我從來沒那麼想 從來沒有 -你就是這麼想
-I never thought that! I never! -You did!
你就是…
You did--
嘿…
Hey, hey. Hey.
沒事…呼吸…
It's okay. It's okay. Breathe, breathe.
卡梅
Cam?
怎麼搞的？
What the fuck, man?
他這種情況不應該回去
He shouldn't go home in that state.
我會跟他談 但他的合同裡有這條
I'll talk to him, but it's in his contract.
我要見他
I need to see him.
我記得當我知道她會沒事的那一刻
I remember when I knew she was gonna be okay.
我曾為特雷西哭泣
I used to cry for Tracy
我想再次見到他
I wanted to see him again
但有時候 生活並不是這樣
But sometimes Sometimes life ain't always the way
有時4月會下雪
Sometimes it snows in April
有時我感覺如此難過
Sometimes I feel so bad
如此難過
So bad
有時我希望生命永不終止
Sometimes I wish life is never-ending
他們說好景不常在 好花不常開
And all good things They say never last
還有愛
And love
直到逝去 才知艱辛
It isn't hard till it's passed
嘿…對剛才的事 我很抱歉
Hey, uh… I'm really sorry about earlier.
我不認為她拋棄了我們
I don't think she abandoned us.
不 你說的有點道理
No, there's something to it.
有點道理
There's something to it.
很久以來她一直想跟我談 以她自己的方式
She'd been trying to talk to me for a long time in her own way.
我以為還有時間
Thought I had more time, I guess.
三個月前我才告訴她我頭暈的事
I just told her about that dizzy spell three months ago.
如果我那時告訴她我頭痛…
If I'd had mentioned the headache back then--
她一定會當天讓我去醫院做掃描
She'd have marched us in for a scan that day.
在擴散之前進行治療
And got to it before it spread.
共同面對
Dealt with it together.
我知道你必須回去看他們 我理解
I know you got to go back and see them. I get it.
做正確的事
Do the right thing here.
七個月後 那個孩子…
In seven months, that baby--
別這樣
Don't do that.
如果你告訴她 你是為了自己這樣做 我在替他們著想
If you tell her, you're saying it for you. I'm saying that for them.
夠了
Enough.
早上好
Morning.
嘿 傑克
Hey, Jack.
嘿…你沒事…
Hey, hey. You're okay. It's okay.
-該死 -你沒事
-Oh, shit. -You're okay.
你沒事
You're okay.
是
Yeah.
你在家期間 監控你的隱形眼鏡信號流
Monitoring your lens feed while you're back at home
是對傑克進行心理評估的重要部分
is an important part of Jack's psychological evaluation.
不會錄製任何內容？
Nothing's ever recorded?
這是我們的政策
That's the policy.
只有傑克才能看信號流？
And only Jack has access to this feed?
沒有人能看到或聽到任何信號
No one sees or hears a thing.
授予存取權限
Access granted.
現在儘量忘記這一切
Now, try your best to forget about all this,
好好享受和他們在一起的時光
and just enjoy your time with them.
我們三天后見 卡梅隆
We'll see you in three days, Cameron.
儘量把一切都拋在腦後 享受在家的時光吧
Try to put everything out of your mind. Just enjoy your time at home.
請一定回來
Do come back.
天啊
Oh, my God.
打電話給他 派輛車去
Call him. Send a car.
天啊
Oh, my God.
站起來
Pick up.
卡梅隆 汽車馬上就到 嘗試站起來
Cameron, there will be a car there in a moment. Try to stand up.
卡梅隆？
Cameron?
我們需要你回來
We're gonna need you to come back.
我剛到家
I just got home.
我們可能只需要改變你的藥物
We might just need to change your medication,
但是我們必須對你進行檢查
but we gotta have a look at you.
我不回去
I'm not going back.
如果你留在那裡 在沒有人監督的情況下 發生一次癲癇發作
If you stay and you have another seizure without supervision,
你可能死在你家人的面前
you could die in front of your family.
去死吧
Fuck you.
去死吧…
Fuck. Fuck.
卡梅隆？
Cameron?
卡梅隆 跟我講話
Cameron, talk to me.
傑克明早去
Jack goes in the morning.
我還沒有完成對他的心理狀態評估
I haven't finished evaluating his psychological state yet.
我對傑克回家感到不放心
I'm not comfortable with Jack going home.
波比在等他回去
Poppy's expecting him back.
-我已經… -傑克準備好了 他明天一早就去
-I have-- -Jack is ready. He goes first thing.
合同裡規定我們可以這麼做
We're covered for this in the contract.
將注明你反對這個決定
It will be noted that you opposed the decision.
讓傑克現在給波比打電話
Tell Jack to call Poppy now.
你在浴室滑倒了 輕微腦震盪 掃描顯示沒問題
You slipped in the shower. Mild concussion. Scan was all good.
明天到家
Home tomorrow.
好吧
All right.
如果這兩周在家裡一切順利 肯定會的
If these two weeks at home go well, which they will,
你關於這個過程的記憶會被抹去
your memory of this process will be removed
我們再也不會在這裡見到你了
and we will not see you here again.
如果卡梅隆醒來 他會監控你的隱形眼鏡信號流
If Cameron wakes up, he will monitor your lens feed.
除非在接下來的兩周有任何問題
But unless there are any issues over the next two weeks,
否則他沒有權力停止
he will not have the option to stop this.
我知道這和我們的計畫不同 不過你準備好了 傑克
I know this isn't as we planned it, but you're ready, Jack.
不要把這兩周當成是考驗
Don't think of these two weeks as a test.
只是回家而已
Just going home.
熊熊？讓我看看你
Bear? Let me see you.
你沒事吧？
Are you okay?
-只是…有點痛 我很好 -是嗎？
-Just-- Just a little bit sore. I'm fine. -Yeah?
腫塊已經退去了
The swelling's gone down.
他們說什麼？
What did they say?
接下來的幾天我會有點頭暈 不過我沒事
I'll be a little bit fuzzy for a few days. But I'm good.
過來
Come here.
你嚇壞我了
You scared me.
我被自己嚇壞了
I scared me.
他在他房間等你
He's waiting for you up in his room.
-誰？ -你兒子
-Who? -Your son.
閉嘴
Shut up.
混蛋
Asshole.
抱歉 我沒忍住
I'm sorry, I had to.
該死 卡梅 別那樣嚇我
Shit, Cam. Don't freak me out like that.
混蛋
Wanker.
-過來 -不
-Come here. -No.
過來
Come here.
-不要 -對不起
-No way. -I'm sorry.
放鬆點
Easy, tiger.
小豬
Pig.
怎麼回事？艾靈頓
What the hell? Ellington?
嘿 夥計
Hey, pal.
我想小豬很生你的氣
Wow, I think Pig's pissed at you
因為你出差還撞到了頭
for leaving town and hitting your head.
它真是不依不饒的 艾靈頓
Wow, he is not letting it go. Ellington.
好了 小豬
Okay, Pig.
我把它放到外面去
I'll stick him outside.
我去看看小博士
I'll go check on Doc.
嘿
Hey.
拉…發生什麼了？
Ra-- What happened?
你昏倒了
You passed out.
你失去知覺幾乎24小時了
You've been unconscious for almost 24 hours.
波比會怎麼想？
What does Poppy think?
一切都很好 卡梅隆
Everything's fine, Cameron.
你這是什麼意思？
What does that mean?
他沒去吧
He's not gone.
在你昏迷的時候 我們在監控一切 一切都很順利
We've been monitoring it all while you were out. Everything's good.
不…我沒有…
No. No, no, no. I didn't get--
我很抱歉事情發生了變化…
I'm so sorry that it happened this way…
我還沒做完 我沒說他可以去
I'm not done. I didn't say he could go.
-但這是正確的決定 -狗屁
-…but it was the right decision. -Bullshit.
我還沒做完
I'm not done!
現在這不是你一個人的事了
Well, it's not about you now.
你說什麼？
Excuse me?
-你現在有個任何人都不會有的機會 -不…
-You have an opportunity that no one gets. -No. No, no, no.
不要自欺欺人 卡梅隆
Don't be blind, Cameron.
-你去死吧 -你快要死了
-Fuck you. -You're dying.
你快要死了
You're dying.
-你快要死了 卡梅… -閉嘴
-You're dying, Cam-- -Stop!
閉嘴
Stop.
傑克準備好了
Jack was ready.
他們很安全
They're in good hands.
他們在你的保護之下
They're in your hands.
我想看視頻
I wanna see the video.
馬上
Now.
你必須停止監視我的家人
And you need to stop watching my family.
我在學校裡知道了紙是木頭
I learned that from school. Paper is wood.
是的
Yes.
-它有…讓我看看 -是嗎？
-It's got some-- Let me see. -Is it?
是有一些木頭
Some wood up there.
是 是的 先生
Yeah. Yes, sir.
-這是唯一的信號流嗎？ -好的
-This the only feed? -Okay.
是
Yes.
我想一個人待著
I'd like to be alone.
不
Nope.
我想讓你多做的一件事是什麼？
So, what's one thing I've been trying to get you to do more of?
-閱讀？ -很好
-Read? -Good.
這裡有一樣小東西給你
Here's a little something for you.
這其實來自你的祖母
Essentially, it's from your grandmother.
我在你這個年齡的時候 她給了我
It's something she gave to me when I was about your age.
打開吧 很有意思的一本
Open it up, it's a good one.
好吧
Okay.
她在裡面寫了點東西
She wrote a little something in it.
我過去非常痛恨安德列 在我們的書裡面這樣做
I used to kill Andre for doing this to our books
在我們小的時候
when we were growing up.
現在我仔細研究他在下面劃線的每一個字
Now I'm, like, poring over every word he underlined.
不知怎麼地 我…
Somehow I'm--
不知怎麼地 我終於可以呼吸了
Somehow I'm finally breathing again.
可是我感覺失去了你 卡梅
But I feel like I've lost you, Cam.
你在你討厭的工作中忙忙碌碌
You keep yourself so busy in a job you hate.
就好像你不在這裡
It's like you're not here.
我不是說這都怪你 你明白嗎？我們都有錯
And I'm not saying you're fully to blame, you know? We're both in this.
我知道我有段時間有些疏遠
I know I checked out for a while.
我知道那讓你害怕
And I know that scared you.
我對此很抱歉 卡梅 真的
And I'm sorry for that, Cam. I am.
那天聽到你說“我撞到了頭”
I mean, hearing you say the words, "I hit my head," the other day…
我不能失去你 卡梅 我沒法活下去
I couldn't lose you, Cam. I couldn't live.
所以我這是在告訴你 我現在不想再沉默了
So this is me telling you that I'm done with the silence now.
我們開始溝通 我們解決問題
We start communicating, and we fix things.
我給你做了一樣東西
I made you a little something.
早日
康復
這太不顧別人的感受了吧
It's really insensitive.
不 我…很抱歉 我…
Oh, no. I'm-- I'm sorry. I--
見鬼 我很…
Oh, shit. I'm so so--
你這個鬼東西
You little shit.
你嚇死我了
You scared me.
你的表情 太…
Your face. It's-- It's--
你嚇壞我了 你真行
You scared me. That was good.
很…棒 真好笑
It is… It's good. Funny.
嘿 沒事的
Hey, oh. It's okay.
你沒事
You're okay.
我在這裡 你沒事
I'm here. You're okay.
鏡片資訊流不可用
他越來越頻繁地摘下隱形眼鏡了
He's taking out the contacts more and more,
不僅是睡覺的時候
not just when he goes to bed.
他不必每時每刻都戴著 它們讓他感覺不舒服
He doesn't have to wear them all the time. They make him feel uncomfortable.
他為你感到難過
He feels badly for you.
但他也對別人監視他的家人感到不舒服
But he also feels uncomfortable having his family watched.
我才不在乎他的不舒服 那是我的家人
I don't give a shit about his comfort. That's my family.
你現在的感受很正常 卡梅隆
What you're feeling right now, Cameron, is normal.
不 不正常
No, it is not.
有什麼事不對勁
Something is wrong.
在過去兩天中 我能感覺到 有什麼不對勁
For the last couple of days, I feel it. Something is off.
在這個階段
At this stage,
無論你在經歷什麼 感受都是正常的 他很好
whatever you're going through, it's normal. He's fine.
好吧
Yeah.
你是怎麼回事？
What's up with you?
鏡片資訊流不可用
寇里 該吃飯了 夥計
Cory, it's time to eat, buddy.
寇里 暫停它
Cory. Pause it.
寇里 快點
Cory, come on.
你覺得怎麼樣？
What do you think?
我喜歡
I like it.
-用佩科里諾芝士代替帕馬森芝士 -太好吃了
-Pecorino instead of Parmesan. -So good.
是的
Yeah.
快點 夥計 立刻 暫停它
Come on, man. Now. Pause it.
沒有那麼鹹 對嗎？稍甜一些？
Less salty, right? Kind of sweeter?
對 很棒
Yeah. It's great.
-你沒事吧 寶貝？ -我沒事
-You okay, babe? -Yeah, I'm fine.
-怎麼了？ -不 我很好…我只是…
-What's up? -No. I'm good. I'm good.
你給我停下
You need to stop!
不
Oh, no.
拒絕訪問
Access denied.
短信息
波比
水管工會晚到 他們說大約2點15分
卡梅
對 他們剛發了資訊 沒事的
給這個傢伙找個好地方 唱片樓上怎麼樣...？
波比
哇 非常好 親愛的
卡梅
那就把它裱起來
波比
太好了 真想快點看看
能買瓶橄欖油嗎？西班牙那種還有洗滌劑
卡梅
好 在商店 會買
波比
另外 今早給我們班看了 我沒事就看看
-好棒 搖擺舞 -我要當哥哥了
-Yeah. The waddle dance. -I'm gonna be a big brother!
-好樣的 -我們在跳搖擺舞
-Good job! -We got the waddle dance.
卡梅
兒子遺傳了我的酷炫動作
波比
大笑
卡梅
♥最佳表情♥
-好樣的 -我們在跳搖擺舞
-Good job! -We got the waddle dance.
卡梅
兒子遺傳了我的酷炫動作
波比
大笑
卡梅
♥最佳表情♥
我愛他
I love him.
回復：新進行中的工作
11月6日 星期二
熊熊 愛你 真高興你又開始創作了
記得打給 節拍畫廊
哇
Wow.
做你需要做的事
Do what you need to do.
嘿…
Hey, hey. Just, um…
小心一點
Just be careful.
嘿 小博士
Hey, Doc.
小博士
Doc.
醒來吧
Wake up.
怎麼了？
What's wrong?
我剛做了一個噩夢 就是想看見你
I just had a really bad nightmare, and I just wanted to see you.
嘿 我有個主意
Hey, I have an idea.
我們假裝這是啤酒 好嗎？
We're going to pretend that this is beer, okay?
我第一次喝啤酒是和我媽媽 不過我年齡比你大多了
My first was with my mom. I was a lot older than you, though.
不過沒關係 我們不會告訴別人
But it's okay. We won't tell anybody.
好
Yeah.
她最喜歡一邊喝啤酒一邊吃這些
And these guys were her favorite thing to eat with beer.
很鹹的毛豆
Edamame with loads of salt.
就著清爽的啤酒
Washed down with a nice, crisp brew.
-味道好極了 -這怎麼吃？
-Yum. -How do you eat it?
瞧？捏住上面這個 從最上面開始一個一個吃
See? Just grab the top one. Start one at a time with the top one.
把它擠出來 對 來吧 對
Pop it out. Yeah, go ahead. Yeah.
-好吃 -不錯 是吧？
-Tastes good. -Good, right?
比看起來好吃
Better than they look.
對 現在和你的啤酒一起吃
Yeah, now try it with your beer.
好吧
Okay.
是蘋果汁 不過…等等…乾杯
Apple juice, but-- Hold up, hold on. Cheers.
長命百歲
Long life for you.
為毛豆乾杯
To edamame.
我再吃一個
I'll just take one more.
過來 夥計
Come here, man.
爸爸 你沒事吧？
You okay, Dad?
讓我看看你 夥計 讓我看看這張臉
Let me look at you, man. Let me look at that face.
對 我沒事
Yeah, I'm okay.
我沒事
I'm okay.
寇里
Cory?
什麼事？
Yes?
我愛你 夥計
I love you, man.
我也愛你 爸爸
I love you too, Dad.
我知道
I know.
乖乖的 小博士
Be good, Doc.
波？
P?
波
P.
我愛你
I love you.
波比 醒醒
Poppy, wake up.
熊熊 怎麼了？
Bear, what's wrong?
你怎麼了？
What's wrong?
沒什麼 我剛…
It's nothing. I just--
我剛做了個噩夢
I just had a really bad dream.
我生了寇里的氣 夢到我失去了一切
I got angry at Cory. Dreamt I lost everything.
寶貝
Oh, baby.
過來
Come here.
天啊 你在發抖 寶貝 你在發抖
God, you're shaking, sweetheart. You're shaking.
感覺太真實了
It felt so real.
寶貝
Oh, sweetheart.
-我們在這裡 對嗎？ -是
-We're here. Yeah? -Yes.
我們現在好多了 對嗎？
We're doing better now. Yeah?
對 我們很好
Yeah, we're doing great.
如果是男孩…
If it's a boy…
我們應該給他起名叫安德列
we should name him Andre.
是 我知道
Yeah. I know.
波比
Poppy?
嗯？
Yeah?
我出過軌
I drifted.
卡梅 別說了 過來
Cam, stop it. Come here.
我很抱歉 我…
I'm so sorry. I just--
聽著
Listen.
我們合好了 對嗎？
We're back, yeah?
這很棒
And it's wonderful.
是嗎？
Yeah?
是
Yeah.
過來
Come here.
來吧 快睡吧
Come on, get to sleep.
謝謝
Thank you.
照顧好他們
Take care of 'em.
我會的
I will.
今天早上 他正式成為卡梅隆特納了
As of this morning, he's officially Cameron Turner.
他將永遠不會知道這些
He'll never know about any of this.
很好
Good.
謝謝你 醫生
Thank you, Doc.
謝謝你
Thank you.
被人遺忘是很痛苦的
It's hard to be left behind.
新客戶快要到了
The new client is about to arrive.
等你跟他談完後 到下面來找我們
Come down to us when you're done speaking with him.
傑克給你留了樣東西
Jack left you something.
寶貝
Babe?
告訴我你愛我
Tell me you love me.
我愛你
I love you.
不…
No, no, no.
卡梅
Cam.
你在做什麼？我在切菜
What are you doing? I'm chopping stuff.
說真的 波
For real, P.
怎麼了？
What?
看著我的眼睛 告訴我你愛我
Look me in the eyes and tell me you love me.
-你在做什麼呀？ -過來 真的
-What are you doing? -Just-- Come on. For real.
我需要聽你說
I need to hear it.
好吧
Okay.
我愛你 卡梅隆特納
I love you, Cameron Turner.
一直是 永遠都是
Always have. And always will.
-怎麼樣？ -太棒了
-How was that? -That was good.
本字幕由Tao5133製作